HERE Publications 6199 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 5, Folder: 19 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Notes: June 25; Copy 2
- Box: 5, Folder: 20 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Notes: September 15; Copy 2
- Box: 5, Folder: 21 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Notes: June 11
- Box: 5, Folder: 22 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Notes: June 28
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Notes: June 28; Copy 2
- Box: 5, Folder: 23 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Notes: June 24
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Notes: June 24; Copy 2
- Box: 5, Folder: 25 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Box: 5, Folder: 26 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Notes: May 16
  - Item 2: Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Notes: May 16; Copy 2
- Box: 5, Folder: 27 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Notes: July 26
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Notes: July 26; Copy 2
- Box: 5, Folder: 28 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Bylaws for the State Councils of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Notes: July 1
  - Item 2: Bylaws for the State Councils of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Notes: July 1; Copy 2
- Box: 5, Folder: 29 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: By-Laws for Local Joint Executive Boards of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Notes: August 17
  - Item 2: Constitution Internationale de IUnion Internationale des Employes dHotel, Restaurant et Commis de bar, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Notes: August 17; Language: Spanish
  - Item 3: International Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: International Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Notes: August 17; Copy 2
- Box: 5, Folder: 30 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    Notes: December; Copy 2
- Box: 6, Folder: 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Notes: July 26; Copy 3
- Box: 6, Folder: 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Notes: August 24
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Notes: August 24; Copy 2
  - Item 3: Constitution of the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Notes: August 24; Copy 3
- Box: 6, Folder: 3 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Notes: August 11
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Notes: August 11; Copy 2
  - Item 3: Constitution of the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Notes: August 11; Copy 3
- Box: 6, Folder: 4 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Constitution de la Union Internacional de Empleados de Hotel y Restaurante, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Notes: August 11; Language: Spanish
- Box: 6, Folder: 5 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Notes: September 9
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Notes: September 9; Copy 2
  - Item 3: Constitution of the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Notes: September 9; Copy 3
- Box: 6, Folder: 6 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Box: 6, Folder: 7 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Constitucion del Sindicato Internacional de Empleados de Restaurantes y Hoteles, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Notes: September 9; Language: Spanish
- Box: 6, Folder: 8 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Notes: September 19
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Notes: September 19; Copy 2
  - Item 3: Constitution of the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Notes: September 19; Copy 3
- Box: 6, Folder: 9 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: UNITE HERE's Merger Convention Constitution - Draft, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Box: 6, Folder: 10 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: By-Laws for the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Box: 6, Folder: 11 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Membership Card and Monthly Stamp Book for the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Box: 6, Folder: 12 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Ritual Book for the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Beverage Dispensers' International Union (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Box: 6, Folder: 13 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The National Purveyor Official Journal, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Author: Bartenders National League of America
    Notes: June; Vol. 1 No. 4
  - Item 2: The National Purveyor Official Journal, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: November; Vol. 2 No. 1
  - Item 3: The National Purveyor Official Journal, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: May; Vol. 2 No. 2
  - Item 4: The National Purveyor Official Journal, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: May; Vol. 2 No. 2; Copy 2
  - Item 5: The National Purveyor Official Journal, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: September; Vol. 11 No. 3
  - Item 6: The National Purveyor Official Journal, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: September; Vol. 11 No. 3; Copy 2
  - Item 7: The National Purveyor Official Journal, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: September; Vol. 11 No. 3; Copy 3
  - Item 8: The National Purveyor Official Journal, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: September; Vol. 11 No. 3; Copy 4
  - Item 9: The National Purveyor Official Journal, 1899 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: March; Vol. 3 No. 1
  - Item 10: The National Purveyor Official Journal, 1899 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: March; Vol. 3 No. 1; Copy 2
  - Item 11: The National Purveyor Official Journal, 1899 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: March; Vol. 3 No. 1; Copy 3
  - Item 12: The National Purveyor Official Journal, 1899 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Notes: September; Vol. 3 No. 3
- Box: 6, Folder: 14 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1900 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Notes: January 15; Vol. 9 No. 1
  - Item 2: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1900 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Notes: March 15; Vol. 9 No. 3
  - Item 3: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1900 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Notes: May 15; Vol. 9 No. 5
  - Item 4: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1900 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Notes: August 15; Vol. 9 No. 8
- Box: 6, Folder: 15 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The American Caterer: Official Magazine of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1896 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Box: 6, Folder: 16 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1900 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Notes: Vol. 9
- Box: 6, Folder: 17 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Notes: Vol. 10
- Box: 6, Folder: 18 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1902 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Notes: Vol. 11
- Box: 6, Folder: 19 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1903 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Notes: Vol. 12
- Box: 6, Folder: 20 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1904 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Notes: Vol. 13
- Box: 6, Folder: 21 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1905 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Notes: Vol. 14
- Box: 6, Folder: 22 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1906 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Notes: Vol. 15
- Box: 6, Folder: 23 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1907 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Notes: Vol. 16
- Box: 6, Folder: 24 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Notes: Vol. 17
- Box: 6, Folder: 25 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Notes: Vol. 18
- Box: 7, Folder: 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1910 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 19
- Box: 7, Folder: 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1911 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 20
- Box: 7, Folder: 3 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Notes: Vol. 21
- Box: 7, Folder: 4 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 22
- Box: 7, Folder: 5 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Notes: Vol. 23
- Box: 7, Folder: 6 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Notes: Vol. 24
- Box: 7, Folder: 7 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. 25
- Box: 7, Folder: 8 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 26
- Box: 7, Folder: 9 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 27
- Box: 8, Folder: 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 28
- Box: 8, Folder: 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 29
- Box: 8, Folder: 3 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: Vol. 30
- Box: 8, Folder: 4 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 31
- Box: 8, Folder: 5 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Notes: Vol. 32
- Box: 8, Folder: 6 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Notes: Vol. 33
- Box: 8, Folder: 7 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1925 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. 34
- Box: 9, Folder: 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 35
- Box: 9, Folder: 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 36
- Box: 9, Folder: 3 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: Vol. 37
- Box: 9, Folder: 4 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Mixer and Server: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 38
- Box: 9, Folder: 5 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Beverage Dispensers International Alliance, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Notes: Vol. 39
- Box: 9, Folder: 6 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Beverage Dispensers International Alliance, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Notes: Vol. 40
- Box: 9, Folder: 7 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Beverage Dispensers International Alliance, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. 41
- Box: 9, Folder: 8 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Beverage Dispensers International Alliance, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 42
- Box: 9, Folder: 9 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Beverage Dispensers International Alliance, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 43
- Box: 9, Folder: 10 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: September October
  - Item 2: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: July - August
  - Item 3: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: May - June
  - Item 4: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: May - June; Copy 2
  - Item 5: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: March - April
  - Item 6: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: March - April; Copy 2
  - Item 7: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: January February
  - Item 8: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: November
  - Item 10: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: October
  - Item 11: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: September
  - Item 12: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: May
  - Item 17: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: February
  - Item 20: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: January
  - Item 21: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 24: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 26: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 27: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 28: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 29: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: May; Copy 2
  - Item 30: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 31: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 32: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 33: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 34: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 35: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 36: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 37: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 38: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 39: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 40: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 41: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: June-July